Grandma, thanks to you,
I may be falling in love
for the first time!
He doesn't need to put on a show.
I prefer him as he is.
You like him as he is?
-Yay!
-Konta! Congratulations!
-You did it!
-Thanks, Rinrin.
Summer festival?
Shall I guide you?
Well, I'll go take a quick look.
Hey, the two of them left together.
The fates of Grim Reapers
and humans do not cross.
With death, their lives are fulfilled.
Mr. Nishigami.
Another hot day, huh?
Yes.
I see.
Orange peels…
How do you make them?
They're surprisingly easy to make.
If you want, we can make them together.
No, I can't do it.
You can!
Here!
Here we go.
What do I do with this?
Huh? Oh, right.
Put it on…
There.
Then, tie this in the front.
All right.
You two, your ice cream is going to melt.
What?
-Something's up…
-Maybe we shouldn't be here?
Yo, Mr. Nishigami!
That apron looks good on you.
-Oh, Midori!
-Yes?
Should I get some more beer?
-Oh, please do. Thanks.
-Okay.
Wait, Konta. I'm going with you. May I?
Wait, really?
Oh, that's a big help. Let's go then!
Yeah, let's go together.
Oh, no. I'm the only one
without any summer romance!
Tetsuro!
Yes?
Going fishing?
I'm going to fish for horse mackerel.
Shall I come along with you?
Sure.
Let's hurry!
-Butterfly.
-Butterfly!
Hey, Konta, how did it go?
The movie. The Great Tenpo Famine?
Oh, they sent over the script.
What are you grinning for?
Well, you see, I actually have lines.
Seriously? That's amazing, Konta!
Well, it's only one line, though.
In order to survive,
you even have to eat grass!
Wow, getting lines is amazing!
It's all thanks to the documentary.
All right, let's race to the sea.
Ready, go!
Hey, wait!
I won't lose, okay?
I'm not going to lose!
Hey!
Mr. Nishigami,
you are surprisingly clumsy.
I'm sorry.
I am not very used to this.
It's okay.
Just take it slow.
Oh, watch your hands.
Okay.
What?
This…
is too thick!
This is a wedge cut.
It's hard to eat.
-I'm sorry. Then, I'll…
-Yes?
What?
So bitter.
I've never done this before.
Fishing is nice, huh.
Just staring blankly at the sea
without thinking about anything.
What a luxury.
Yes.
After coming here,
I've discovered how fun fishing is.
I mean, it's certainly better than SNS.
Oh, you mean social media.
I don't use any.
You know, my ex,
he checks my social media quite a bit,
and he leaves likes often.
Oh, here it comes!
-Here it comes!
-You got something! All right!
Oh, wow!
Wow!
You got the first fish!
Nice.
And… posted.
You're posting it?
Oh! I did it without thinking!
Yikes, I'm addicted.
But I'm glad it wasn't a total bust.
Midori will be happy.
What? Bust?
It's a fishing term.
If you don't catch a single fish,
it's called a bust.
But why Midori?
Oh, nothing.
It's just that Midori likes cooking,
so I thought she would be happy.
I see.
All right.
Let's catch a bunch
and have Midori make sashimi out of them.
Let's buy some sake on the way back.
-A sashimi party.
-Yeah!
Party!
Mr. Nishigami…
Do you have a girlfriend?
A girlfriend?
No.
I have no one like that.
I see.
Oh, by the way, I've never had one either.
Surprising, right?
I'm already 28.
It's a red flag, isn't it?
Is that so?
Heave-ho.
It's so windy today.
Hup.
-Rinrin!
-Yes?
-What?
-I bought juice.
-Huh? What kind of juice?
-Take a guess!
What could it be? Coffee…
-Coke.
-Oh, it's Coke.
-You only got the "co" right.
-I did. Thank you.
You were shaking it, right?
-Did I? It will be fine.
-Will it?
-No! What terrible luck!
-No!
-It's all over me!
-Sorry, Rinrin!
Hey, so…
What?
What exactly
is our relationship right now?
What kind of relationship…
Well, about that…
The other day, you know, during Obon,
we, you know…
Do you…
think we can be a couple?
"A woman's heart
is a deep ocean of secrets."
Hey!
Is that Rose's famous line from Titanic?
Truly an actor!
You remembered it from just a line.
No, I love Titanic!
I remember lots of lines from it.
So you watched the dubbed version?
Well, of course. I don't know English.
Between Rose and Jack,
do you think the concept
of "dating" even existed?
I don't know.
They fell in love instantly,
and before they could think about dating,
the ship went bam!
Well, let's do fun things together,
then I'll think about us dating.
Wait, so…
I have a chance?
All right, let's practice acting.
-What?
-Oh!
I want to play Titanic on that boat.
Huh, on that fishing boat?
-Yeah!
-Sure.
-Really?
-Wait, Rinrin, your bag!
-The sea is so vast and blue.
-Vast and blue!
Konta!
What, Rinrin?
When you become famous and rich,
can you make me your stay-at-home wife?
What?
Is this a proposal?
If you become a popular actor,
I won't have to work anymore, right?
I can just relax here
like this forever, right?
All right.
-Rinrin, here.
-Oh, okay.
There you go.
I will do my best!
For you, Rinrin!
I'll be the biggest star!
Good luck!
Rinrin!
What?
Can I say something
I like about you, Rinrin?
Sure!
Rinrin,
your skin is so fair!
What are those two doing?
For some reason,
when people stand in front of the sea,
they can't help but reenact Titanic.
Huh? Who are you?
How is it?
Enjoying the life you have left?
It's nice to be young.
The life we have left?
Yes, we're having fun…
fishing.
Oh, I see.
Okay. That's a good thing.
It's good.
-Huh?
-It's good.
It's nice to be young…
Do you think she and Konta are dating?
They kissed. It doesn't
necessarily mean they're dating.
What?
What do you mean by that?
By the way,
you're interested in Midori, aren't you?
What?
Huh, wait?
Am I?
You don't even know?
You like her, for sure.
Look, you're even fishing for her sake.
Midori is a good girl.
She's a hard worker, and she's cute.
I like her too.
But she probably…
Sun-drying is nice, isn't it?
They absorb a lot of sunlight,
so I'm sure they will turn out delicious.
By drying them out like this,
what will you achieve, in the end?
I don't really understand it.
I'm home!
Welcome home.
-Midori, look.
-What is it?
-Midori.
-Hm?
-We got a huge catch!
-What?
Oh, wow!
Now work your magic, Chef.
I'm raring to go.
I'll help too.
-Okay.
-We've got to make sashimi.
-Yeah!
-Sashimi!
Sashimi!
-What about fried?
-Sounds good too!
Fried!
Make nanbanzuke!
Nanbanzuke!
Tetsuro, bring out the plates.
Also, please chill the alcohol.
Got it.
As for you, Mr. Nishigami,
can you cut some cucumber
to garnish the sashimi?
-Here.
-Understood.
Don't cut it too thick like earlier, okay?
Yes.
But…
Cucumbers, even when thick,
are delicious, right?
Well, true.
-Look at this.
-What a nice photo!
-Oh, I'm so embarrassed! My dimples!
-They're cute!
-Dimples are so cute!
-I have one too.
No, you don't.
Somehow, this vacation
is making everyone lovey-dovey.
Now then, put your hands together.
Put your hands together.
Let's eat.
Let's eat!
-Tsumugi, pass the soy sauce.
-Okay.
Tetsuro, shall I take this for you?
-Thank you.
-Mr. Nishigami, here is the wasabi.
-It looks good.
-Thank you.
-All right, let's eat.
-Yum!
When I remember that I caught these,
they taste twice as good.
-Tsumugi caught two mackerels by herself.
-Really?
-I might have a knack for fishing.
-Sure.
By the way, Rinrin, Konta,
you two were reenacting Titanic, right?
You were watching? How embarrassing.
It's not embarrassing.
In that moment,
we were totally Rose and Jack.
What were you doing, Midori?
I was making summer orange peels
with Mr. Nishigami, right?
I had fun.
Me too.
So good.
Here.
It's so nice.
There's salad too.
-Thank you.
-Here you go, the usual salad.
Thanks for the salad.
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
Be careful on your way home.
See you tomorrow.
Yeah. See you tomorrow.
AI.
This is Tetsuro.
Right now, I'm on vacation.
And when I see a woman
I'm spending time with
looking happy with another person,
another man…
my chest tightens.
And before I know it, I…
I find myself thinking only about her.
What is this feeling?
Tetsuro.
That feeling of yours is most likely love.
Love?
By the way, you mentioned
you are on vacation.
When humans are placed
in an unusual environment,
they develop romantic feelings
more easily.
Since AIs do not have emotions,
we cannot experience love or jealousy.
We don't have vacations either.
Vacations are a human privilege.
A human privilege?
On vacation, people fall in love.
It's like a principle.
A vacation
principle?
Grim Reaper.
Your recent actions
have been unacceptable.
Do you understand what I mean?
I'm not sure.
Back during Obon,
I was relieved that you understood
your position as a Grim Reaper,
but now you're getting
friendly again with those people.
The Sea God reported to me as much.
What's wrong, Grim Reaper?
Surely…
You haven't forgotten
your mission, have you?
There is no way I would do such a thing.
Then why are you being their friend?
As a Grim Reaper,
there is no need for you
to have bonds with humans.
Furthermore, given your position,
falling in love with a human
is out of the question.
Do you understand?
I do.
A typhoon is coming soon.
Because of it, a landslide will occur,
and that villa will be destroyed.
Those five you are
so close with will all die.
Witnessing their demise
is your duty as a Grim Reaper.
Don't forget that.
Be careful on your way home.
See you tomorrow.
It's finally here.
Midori's first love.
Hey, Midori, seriously?
Mr. Nishigami hasn't come
for the past two days.
He isn't playing
with Midori's feelings, right?
Mr. Nishigami…
You said, "See you tomorrow"…
Because of this vacation,
it's now easier for us to fall in love.
Why not make a move on Midori?
I…
Mr. Nishigami…
I'm the one at fault here.
Seriously?
What is that supposed to mean?
So it was all my misunderstanding?
Mr. Nishigami, could it be…
you have come to dislike us?
Subtitle translation by: Nix S.